Harvard University. Official register of Harvard University, 1900-2008: an inventory
Official register of Harvard University, 1900-2008
- Volume XXXVII, issued 1940
  - 4. Information in regard to the freshman halls, with floor plans and prices, February 16, 1940 (HU 75.25 Box 67)
  - 5. Concentration field of biochemical sciences, containing an announcement for 1940-1941, March 1, 1940 (HU 75.25 Box 67)
  - 6. Rules relating to College studies, March 2, 1940 (HU 75.25 Box 67)
  - 7. Provisional announcement of the courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences during 1940-1941, March 4, 1940 (HU 75.25 Box 67)
  - 8. Department of Architectural Sciences, containing an announcement for 1940-1941, March 5, 1940 (HU 75.25 Box 67)
  - 9. Admission to Harvard College, containing requirements for the academic year 1940-1941, March 6, 1940 (HU 75.25 Box 67)
  - 10. The houses, general information for the Class of 1943, March 9, 1940 (HU 75.25 Box 67)
  - 11. Department of Engineering Sciences, containing an announcement for 1940-1941, March 26, 1940 (HU 75.25 Box 67)
  - 12. Issue containing the report of the President of Harvard College and reports of departments for 1938-1939, March 30, 1940 (HU 75.25 Box 64)
  - 13. Harvard Summer School of Education, workshops, April 2, 1940 (HU 75.25 Box 68)
  - 14. Department of Sociology, containing an announcement for 1940-1941, April 3, 1940 (HU 75.25 Box 67)
  - 15. Harvard Summer School of Education, opportunities for study in the philosophy of education, the history of education, comparative eduction, April 6, 1940 (HU 75.25 Box 68)
  - 16. Harvard Summer School of education, opportunities for study of the teaching of English, April 8, 1940 (HU 75.25 Box 68)
  - 17. Harvard Summer School of Education, to administrators and supervisors of secondary education, April 9, 1940 (HU 75.25 Box 68)
  - 18. Summer School news, April 15, 1940 (HU 75.25 PF Box 1)
  - 19. Harvard Divinity School bulletin, issue containing the annual lectures and book reviews for the academic year 1939-1940, April 16, 1940 (HU 75.25 Box 67)
  - 20. Harvard Summer School, opportunities for study in principles of teaching and the teaching of school subjects, April 17, 1940 (HU 75.25 Box 68)
  - 21. Harvard Summer School, opportunities for study in remedial reading, statistical methods, educational psychology, educational measurement, training of mentally deficient children, April 18, 1940 (HU 75.25 Box 68)
  - 22. Harvard Summer School conference, religious principles and contemporary national and international issues, April 20, 1940 (HU 75.25 Box 68)
  - 23. Harvard Summer School, alumni institute, April 22, 1940 (HU 75.25 Box 68)
  - 24. The Law School, including courses of instruction for 1939-1940, April 22, 1940 (HU 75.25 Box 67)
    Cover reads, "1940-1941."
  - 25. The Graduate School of Design, Departments of Architecture, Landscape Architecture and Regional Planning, with courses of instruction, 1940-1941, April 23, 1940 (HU 75.25 Box 67)
  - 26. Department of Mathematics, containing an announcement for 1940-1941, April 24, 1940 (HU 75.25 Box 67)
  - 27. Graduate School of Business Administration, April 25, 1940 (HU 75.25 Box 67)
  - 28. Studies in the freshman year in Harvard College, April 26, 1940 (HU 75.25 Box 67)
  - 29. The Law School, including courses of instruction for 1940-1941, April 29, 1940 (HU 75.25 Box 67)
  - 30. Department of the Fine Arts, containing an announcement for 1940-1941, April 30, 1940 (HU 75.25 Box 67)
  - 31. Announcement of the courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences during 1940-1941, first edition, May 21, 1940 (HU 75.25 Box 67)
  - 32. Courses and degrees in comparative philology, May 22, 1940 (HU 75.25 Box 67)
  - 33. Department of Philosophy, containing an announcement for 1940-1941, May 23, 1940 (HU 75.25 Box 68)
  - 34. The Divinity School, including courses of instruction for 1940-1941, May 24, 1940 (HU 75.25 Box 68)
  - 35. Department of Anthropology, containing an announcement for 1940-1941, May 25, 1940 (HU 75.25 Box 68)
  - 36. Division of Medical Sciences, 1940-1941, May 27, 1940 (HU 75.25 Box 68)
  - 37. Faculty of Arts and Sciences, Faculty of Education, Master of Arts in Teaching, May 28, 1940 (HU 75.25 Box 68)
  - 38. Harvard Summer School conference on religious principles and contemporary national and international issues, May 29, 1940 (HU 75.25 Box 68)
  - 39. Summer School news, June 7, 1940 (HU 75.25 PF Box 1)
  - 40. Graduate School of Engineering, including announcement of courses under the Faculty of Engineering for 1940-1941, June 21, 1940 (HU 75.25 Box 68)
  - 41. Department of Psychology, containing an announcement for 1940-1941, June 22, 1940 (HU 75.25 Box 68)
  - 42. Graduate School of Education, including courses of instruction for 1940-1941, June 24, 1940 (HU 75.25 Box 68)
  - 43. Department of Physics, containing an announcement for 1940-1941, June 25, 1940 (HU 75.25 Box 68)
  - 44. Division of Ancient Languages, Department of the Classics and Department of Indic Philology, containing an announcement for 1940-1941, June 26, 1940 (HU 75.25 Box 68)
  - 45. The Harvard School of Public Health, including courses of instruction for 1940-1941, June 27, 1940 (HU 75.25 Box 68)
  - 46. Department of Military Science, containing an announcement for 1940-1941, June 28, 1940 (HU 75.25 Box 68)
  - 47. Department of Chemistry, containing an announcement for 1940-1941, June 29, 1940 (HU 75.25 Box 69)
  - 48. Graduate School of Public Administration, containing an announcement for 1940-1941, July 1, 1940 (HU 75.25 Box 68)
  - 49. Harvard College, rank list for freshman class (Class of 1943), July 2, 1940 (HU 75.25 Box 68)
  - 50. Department of Romance Languages and Literatures, containing an announcement for 1940-1941, August 1, 1940 (HU 75.25 Box 68)
  - 51. Division of History, Government, and Economics, containing an announcement for 1940-1941, August 15, 1940 (HU 75.25 Box 68)
  - 52. Department of Music, September 3, 1940 (HU 75.25 Box 68)
  - 53. Department of Naval Science and Tactics, containing an announcement for 1940-1941, September 4, 1940 (HU 75.25 Box 68)
  - 54. Department of Astronomy, containing an announcement for 1940-1941, October 1, 1940 (HU 75.25 Box 68)
  - 55. Announcement of the courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences during 1940-1941, second edition, October 2, 1940 (HU 75.25 Box 68)
  - 56. Department of English, containing an announcement for 1940-1941, November 1, 1940 (HU 75.25 Box 68)
  - 57. The Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, containing an announcement for 1940-1941, November 5, 1940 (HU 75.25 Box 68)
  - 58. Department of Germanic Languages and Literature, containing an announcement of courses in Germanic and Slavic languages, literatures and philology for 1940-1941, November 6, 1940 (HU 75.25 Box 68)
  - 59. Department of Biology and related institutions, containing an announcement of courses in Germanic and Slavic languages, literatures and philology for 1940-1941, December 2, 1940 (HU 75.25 Box 68)
  - 60. Division of Geological Sciences, Departments of Geology and Geography, and Mineralogy and Petrography, containing an announcement for 1940-1941, December 3, 1940 (HU 75.25 Box 68)
  - 61. General catalogue issue, December 4, 1940 (HU 75.25 Box 67)
  - 62. The Harvard Medical School, with an announcement of the Harvard Medical School and the Harvard School of Dental Medicine for 1941-1942, December 5, 1940 (HU 75.25 Box 69)
  - 63. The Law School, including courses of instruction and students for 1940-1941, December 6, 1940 (HU 75.25 Box 69)
  - 64. Graduate School of Business Administration, mid-year session, December 7, 1940 (HU 75.25 Box 69)
  - 65. Harvard College list of scholarships awarded for 1940-1941, December 9, 1940 (HU 75.25 Box 69)
- Volume XXXVIII, issued 1941
  No. 66 was never published.
  - 1. Expenses and financial aids in Harvard College, January 2, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 69)
  - 2. Summer School of Arts and Sciences and of Education, preliminary announcement, January 3, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 69)
  - 3. Admission to Harvard College, containing requirements for the academic year, 1941-1942, January 4, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 69)
  - 4. General information about Harvard College, February 4, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 69)
  - 5. Information in regard to the freshman halls, with floor plans and pricing, February 17, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 69)
  - 6. Summer School of Arts and Sciences and of Education, March 1, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 69)
  - 7. Fellowships and scholarships administered by the Committee on General Scholarships and the Sheldon Fund, March 3, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 69)
  - 8. Harvard Summer School, an unusual program for teachers of the social studies, March 4, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 70)
  - 9. Department of Engineering Sciences, containing an announcement for 1941-1942, March 5, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 69)
  - 10. The houses, general information for the Class of 1944, March 10, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 70)
  - 11. Provisional announcement of the courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences during 1941-1942, March 19, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 69)
  - 12. Rules relating to College studies, March 20, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 69)
  - 13. Harvard Summer School, enlarged program in educational administration, March 21, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 70)
  - 14. Harvard Summer School, opportunities for study in remedial reading, statistical methods, educational psychology, educational measurement, problems of growth and behavior of children, April 3, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 70)
  - 15. Harvard Summer School, an unusual program for teachers of art, April 4, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 70)
  - 16. Harvard Summer School, opportunities for study in principles of teaching and the teaching of school subjects, April 5, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 70)
  - 17. Harvard Summer School, opportunities for study of the teaching of English, April 7, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 70)
  - 18. Faculty of Arts and Sciences, Faculty of Education, Master of Arts in teaching, April 8, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 69)
  - 19. Harvard Summer School, opportunities for study in the philosophy of education, the history of education, comparative education, April 10, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 70)
  - 20. Issue containing the report of the President of Harvard College and reports of departments for 1939-1940, April 10, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 70)
  - 21. Harvard Summer School workshop in secondary school administration and youth problems, April 11, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 70)
  - 22. Harvard Summer School, workshop in education, April 12, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 70)
  - 23. The Dental School, with an announcement of the School of Dental Medicine, April 14, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 69)
  - 24. Graduate School of Business Administration, April 15, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 70)
  - 24, Part 2. Business Administration, April 15, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 70)
  - 25. Summer School, news, April 16, 1941 (HU 75.25 PF Box 1)
  - 26. Harvard Summer School, alumni institute, April 17, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 70)
  - 27. Harvard Divinity School bulletin, issue containing the annual lectures and book reviews for the year 1940-1941, April 22, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 70)
  - 28. Preliminary announcement, Second New England Conference on Tomorrow's Children, April 23, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 70)
  - 29. Harvard Summer School, speech and dramatic arts, April 24, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 70)
  - 30. Department of Philosophy, containing an announcement for 1941-1942, April 29, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 69)
  - 31. Department of Architectural Sciences, containing an announcement for 1941-1942, April 30, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 69)
  - 32. Fifth Annual Conference of Elementary School Principals, May 21, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 69)
  - 33. Department of Anthropology, containing an announcement for 1941-1942, May 22, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 69)
  - 34. Harvard Summer School conference on religion and the world today, May 23, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 70)
  - 35. Second New England Conference on Tomorrow's Children, May 24, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 70)
  - 36. Department of Physics, containing an announcement for 1941-1942, May 26, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 69)
  - 37. Division of Ancient Languages, Department of the Classics and Department of Indic Philology, containing an announcement for 1941-1942, May 27, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 69)
  - 38. Graduate School of Education, including courses of instruction for 1941-1942, May 28, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 69)
  - 39. Department of Psychology, containing an announcement for 1941-1942, May 29, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 69)
  - 40. Summer School, news, June 5, 1941 (HU 75.25 PF Box 1)
  - 41. The Harvard School of Public Health, including courses of instruction for 1941-1942, June 21, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 69)
  - 42. Graduate School of Engineering, including announcement of courses under the Faculty of Engineering for 1941-1942, June 23, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 69)
  - 43. The Divinity School, including courses of instruction for 1941-1942, June 24, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 69)
  - 44. Department of Mathematics, containing an announcement for 1941-1942, June 25, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 69)
  - 45. Harvard College rank list for freshman class (Class of 1944), June 26, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 69)
  - 46. The Law School, including courses of instruction for 1941-1942, June 27, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 69)
  - 47. Department of Romance Languages and Literatures, containing an announcement for 1941-1942, June 28, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 69)
  - 48. Department of Naval Science and Tactics, containing an announcement for 1941-1942, June 30, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 69)
  - 49. Department of Sociology, containing an announcement for 1941-1942, June 30, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 69)
  - 50. Graduate School of Public Administration, containing an announcement for 1941-1492, July 31, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 69)
  - 51. Regulations for degree of Ph.D. in History and Philosophy of Religion, August 7, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 69)
  - 52. Department of Music, August 14, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 69)
  - 53. Faculty of Arts and Sciences, Faculty of Education, Master of Arts in Teaching, September 2, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 69)
  - 54. Final announcement of the courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences during 1941-1942, September 18, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 69)
  - 55. Supplement to the announcement of the Department of Chemistry, containing information for 1941-1941, October 1, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 70)
  - 56. Directory of officers and students, October 17, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 70)
  - 57. Studies in the freshman year in Harvard College, November 5, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 69)
  - 58. The Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, containing an announcement for 1941-1942, November 6, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 69)
  - 60. Department of English, containing an announcement for 1941-1942, December 1, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 69)
  - 61. Division of History, Government, and Economics, containing an announcement for 1941-1942, December 1, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 70)
  - 62. Department of Biology and related institutions, including courses of instruction for 1941-1942, December 3, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 70)
  - 63. Faculty of Arts and Sciences, Faculty of Education, Master of Arts in Teaching, December 4, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 70)
  - 64. Graduate School of Business Administration, mid-year session, December 5, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 70)
  - 65. The Harvard Forest, general information and courses of instruction for 1942-1943, December 30, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 70)
  - 67. The Harvard Medical School, with an announcement of the Harvard Medical School and the Harvard School of Dental Medicine for 1942-1943, December 31, 1941 (HU 75.25 Box 70)
- Volume XXXIX, issued 1942
  Nos. 21, 26-31, 34-37, 46-48, and 56 were never published.
  - 1. Opportunities for special training during the war, January 20, 1942 (HU 75.25 Box 72)
  - 2. Harvard Law School, special announcement, January 29, 1942 (HU 75.25 Box 72)
  - 3. The war-time program at Harvard, January 30, 1942 (HU 75.25 Box 72)
  - 4. Department of Germanic Languages and Literatures, containing an announcement of courses in Germanic and Slavic languages, literatures and philology for 1941-1942, February 4, 1942 (HU 75.25 Box 71)
  - 5. Issue containing the report of the President of Harvard College and reports of departments for 1940-1941, February 4, 1942 (HU 75.25 Box 71)
  - 6. Department of Engineering Sciences, containing an announcement for 1942-1943, March 13, 1942 (HU 75.25 Box 71)
  - 7. Expenses and financial aids in Harvard College, March 14, 1942 (HU 75.25 Box 71)
  - 8. Freshmen and the houses, March 16, 1942 (HU 75.25 Box 71)
  - 9. The Dental School, March 18, 1942 (HU 75.25 Box 71)
  - 10. Preliminary announcement of the courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences during 1942-1943, March 19, 1942 (HU 75.25 Box 71)
  - 11. Department of Physics, containing an announcement for 1942-1943, March 23, 1942 (HU 75.25 Box 71)
  - 12. Regulations for the degree of Ph.D. in History and Philosophy of Religion, March 31, 1942 (HU 75.25 Box 71)
  - 13. Faculty of Arts and Sciences, Faculty of Education, Masters of Art in Teaching, March 30, 1942 (HU 75.25 Box 71)
  - 14. Harvard Divinity School bulletin, issue containing the annual lectures and book reviews for the year 1941-1942, April 14, 1942 (HU 75.25 Box 71)
  - 15. Announcement of courses under the Faculty of Engineering for the summer of 1942, April 15, 1942 (HU 75.25 Box 72)
  - 16. Final announcement of the courses of instruction offered in the summer term, 1942, April 20, 1942 (HU 75.25 Box 71)
  - 17. Studies in the freshman year, April 22, 1942 (HU 75.25 Box 71)
  - 18. Department of Philosophy, containing an announcement for 1942-1943, April 27, 1942 (HU 75.25 Box 71)
  - 19. The war-time program at Harvard, April 29, 1942 (HU 75.25 Box 71)
  - 20. Department of Comparative Philology, April 28, 1942 (HU 75.25 Box 72)
  - 22. Department of Music, April 24, 1942 (HU 75.25 Box 71)
  - 23. Graduate School of Public Administration, containing an announcement for 1942-1943, April 21, 1942 (HU 75.25 Box 71)
  - 24. Department of Psychology, containing an announcement for 1942-1943, April 21, 1942 (HU 75.25 Box 71)
  - 25. Graduate School of Engineering, April 21, 1942 (HU 75.25 Box 71)
  - 32. Graduate School of Design, courses in city planning, May 1, 1942 (HU 75.25 Box 71)
  - 33. Harvard School of Public Health, including courses of instruction for 1942-1943, May 4, 1942 (HU 75.25 Box 71)
  - 38. Graduate School of Education, including courses of instruction for 1942-1943, May 28, 1942 (HU 75.25 Box 71)
  - 40. Graduate School of Engineering, announcement of courses under the Faculty of Engineering for 1942-1943, June 22, 1942 (HU 75.25 Box 71)
  - 41. Graduate School of Business Administration, June 1, 1942 (HU 75.25 Box 71)
  - 42. Faculty of Arts and Sciences, Faculty of Education, Master of Arts in Teaching, June 3, 1942 (HU 75.25 Box 71)
  - 43. Harvard Law School, special announcement,June22, 1942 (HU 75.25 Box 71)
  - 44. The Divinity School, including courses of instruction for 1942-1943, June 24, 1942 (HU 75.25 Box 71)
  - 45. Division of History, Government and Economics, containing an announcement for 1942-1943, June 30, 1942 (HU 75.25 Box 71)
  - 49. Department of Sociology, containing an announcement for 1942-1943, July 22, 1942 (HU 75.25 Box 71)
  - 50. Department of Romance Languages and Literatures, containing an announcement for 1942-1943, July 30, 1942 (HU 75.25 Box 71)
  - 51. The Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, containing an announcement for 1942-1943, August 26, 1942 (HU 75.25 Box 71)
  - 52. Department of Mathematics, containing an announcement for 1942-1943, August 31, 1942 (HU 75.25 Box 71)
  - 53. Final announcement of the courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences during 1942-1943, September 23, 1942 (HU 75.25 Box 72)
  - 54. Department of English, containing an announcement for 1942-1943, September 28, 1942 (HU 75.25 Box 71)
  - 55. Directory of officers and students, October 24, 1942 (HU 75.25 Box 71)
  - 57. Statement of the Treasurer of Harvard College for the fiscal year 1941-1942, November 14, 1942 (HU 75.25 Box 70)
  - 58. The Harvard Medical School, with an announcement of the Harvard Medical School and the Harvard School of Dental Medicine for 1943, November 30, 1942 (HU 75.25 Box 71)
  - 60. General catalogue issue, December 8, 1942 (HU 72.25 Box 71)
- Volume XL, issued 1943
  Nos. 2 and 19 were never published.
  - 1. Studies in the freshman year in Harvard College, supplementary information for the spring term, 1943, January 22, 1943 (HU 75.25 Box 73)
  - 3. Harvard College, 1943-1944, February 23, 1943 (HU 75.25 Box 73)
  - 4. Announcement of the courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences during 1943-1944, March 29, 1943 (HU 75.25 Box 73)
  - 5. Supplement to the announcement of Department of Physics, containing information for 1943-1944, April 1, 1943 (HU 75.25 Box 73)
  - 6. Announcement of the courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Engineering, 1943-1944, April 15, 1943 (HU 75.25 Box 73)
  - 7. The Dental School, April 19, 1943 (HU 75.25 Box 73)
  - 8. Workshop in Education, 1943, May 15, 1943 (HU 75.25 Box 73)
  - 9. Courses in education, May 16, 1943 (HU 75.25 Box 73)
  - 10. Studies in the freshman year, May 28, 1943 (HU 75.25 Box 73)
  - 11. Harvard College in war time, June 24, 1943 (HU 75.25 Box 73)
  - 12. Graduate School of Education, including courses of instruction for 1943-1944, June 23, 1943 (HU 75.25 Box 73)
  - 13. Graduate School of Public Administration, containing an announcement for 1943-1944, June 30, 1943 (HU 75.25 Box 73)
  - 14. Directory of officers, students, and men enrolled in the Navy V-12 unit, July 27, 1943 (HU 75.25 Box 73)
  - 15. Harvard School of Public Health, including courses of instruction for 1943-1944, July 28, 1943 (HU 75.25 Box 73)
  - 16. Expenses and financial aids in Harvard College, July 31, 1943 (HU 75.25 Box 73)
  - 17. The Divinity School, including courses of instruction for 1943-1944, August 16, 1943 (HU 75.25 Box 73)
  - 18. The Law School, including courses of instruction for 1943-1944, August 30, 1943 (HU 75.25 Box 73)
  - 20. Statement of the Treasurer of Harvard College for the fiscal year 1942-1943, September 28, 1943 (HU 75.25 Box 72)
  - 21. Announcement of the courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences during the winter and spring terms, 1943-1944, September 22, 1943 (HU 75.25 Box 73)
- Volume XLI, issued 1944
  Incomplete. Lacks No. 18. Statement of the Treasurer of Harvard College for the fiscal year 1943-1944, August 23, 1944.
  - 1. Harvard Divinity School bulletin, issue containing the annual lectures and book reviews for the year 1942-1943, January 3, 1944 (HU 75.25 Box 74)
  - 2. The Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, January 15, 1944 (HU 75.25 Box 74)
  - 3. The Law School, including courses of instruction for spring term 1944, January 25, 1944 (HU 75.25 Box 74)
  - 4. The Dental School, February 11, 1944 (HU 75.25 Box 74)
  - 5. General catalogue issue, February 28, 1944 (HU 75.25 Box 73)
  - 6. Faculty of Arts and Sciences, Faculty of Education, Master of Arts in Teaching, March 9, 1944 (HU 75.25 Box 74)
  - 7. Announcement of the courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences for the academic year 1944-1945, March 30, 1944 (HU 75.25 Box 74)
  - 8. The Harvard Medical School, with an announcement of the Harvard School of Dental Medicine for 1944-1945, March 31, 1944 (HU 75.25 Box 74)
  - 9. Graduate School of Engineering, including announcement of courses under the Faculty of Engineering for 1944-1945, April 2, 1944 (HU 75.25 Box 74)
  - 10. Studies in the freshman year, April 25, 1944 (HU 75.25 Box 74)
  - 11. Harvard Film Service, catalogue of educational films, June 22, 1944 (HU 75.25 Box 74)
  - 12. Graduate School of Education, including courses of instruction for 1944-1945, June 23, 1944 (HU 75.25 Box 74)